loupiote.com 2017-06-06

# Loupiote Blog - Photography by Tristan Savatier: Privacy Policy and Use of Web Cookies

| 

###  [Privacy Policy and Use of Web Cookies](http://blog.loupiote.com/2009/03/privacy-policy.html)

Privacy Policy for the domains loupiote.com, playa-dust.com, dog-meat.net and all their sub-domains.  
**  
**Information that we may gather  
  
If you browse through our websites without entering any personal data, we will gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and cannot be linked back to you unless you decide at some point to identify yourself.  

If you are only browsing, we collect the following information: your IP address (Internet Protocol), informations about the browser, the computer or device, the operating system used to access our sites, the date and time you access our sites, the pages you visit (click-through), and if you linked to our website from another website, the URL of that website page (the "Referrer"), the search terms you used for finding our web pages, as well as additional information related to your visit. If you enter search terms or other information in forms on our pages, we may gather this information. If you contact us via email, we may gather all the information received in the email, including your name and email address.  
  
We share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners.

**What we may do with your personally  identifiable information**

We will only use personally identifiable information that you provided us explicitly (such as your name and email) to communicate with you. We will not give or sell your personally identifiable information to any third-party. Note that some of the information that you enter on our pages (e.g. comments) may be captured by third-party companies. See details below.

**Web cookies**

We use web cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features, to analyse our traffic and to improve your experience.  
  
Web cookies are small chunks of data created by a web server, delivered through a web browser, and temporarily stored on your computer. They provide a means for websites that you visit to keep a "state" of information during a browsing cession. No personally-identifiable information is collected by or linked to any of the cookies delivered by our sites. 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Web beacons

We use web beacons. A web beacon is an object that is embedded in a web page or e-mail and is usually invisible to the user but allows checking that a user has viewed the page. To learn more about web beacons, visit [http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_bug](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_bug).

Third-party advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our websites. These companies may gather information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number or any personally identifiable information) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. To provide more relevant ads, advertising company use, among other things, web cookies and web beacons (to track your browsing habits), as well as your IP address (for geo-location), the search terms you used to reach our pages and the search terms you entered on our pages, and the Referrers. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check their respective privacy policies ([Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html), [AdMob](http://helpcenter.admob.com/content/privacy-policy), [Chitika](http://chitika.com/privacy_policy.php), [Clicksor](http://clicksor.com/), [AdBrite](http://adbrite.com/)).

Google uses the DART cookie to serve ads to our users based on their previous visits to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). View also [ How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/).

Third-party traffic analysis  

We use third-party traffic analysis companies to monitor the traffic on our websites. These companies may use web cookies, web beacons and gather other information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number or any personally identifiable information) to analyse the traffic source and patterns on our sites. If you would like more information about the information being captured by those third-party traffic analysis companies, check their respective privacy policies ([Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html), [Whos.amung.us](http://whos.amung.us/privacy/)).

Third-party companies managing user comments and social networks

We use third-party companies to allow you to enter comments on our web pages and blogs, to recommend pages to your social networks connections (e.g. Facebook, Google+). These companies may use web cookies, web beacons and gather other information to perform their service. If you decide to enter information in the comments forms, those third-party companies will capture this information, such as your name, email or other personally identifiable information that you will provide. For more information, please check their privacy policies (e.g. [Disqus](http://disqus.com/), [JS-Kit](http://js-kit.com/about/policy.html), [Blogger](http://www.blogger.com/privacy), [Facebook](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php?app_id=113869198637480), [Google](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/), [Twitter](https://twitter.com/privacy)).

Third-party companies providing other services

We use third-party companies to offer other services such as ordering prints and digital file licensing. These companies may use web cookies, web beacons and gather other information to perform their service. If you decide to enter information in the forms, shopping carts or web pages managed by these companies, those third-party companies will capture this information, such as your name, email, credit-card number or other personally identifiable information that you will provide. For more information, please check their privacy policies ([Fotomoto](http://www.fotomoto.com/help/privacy), [Getty-Images](http://www.gettyimages.com/)).

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**   

This privacy policy is not contractual but is a statement of our current policy. We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time, for any reason. Users are encouraged to check our site frequently to review the current privacy policy in effect.

This privacy policy was last updated: August 3, 2015.

|   
---|---|---
